在这个短课程中，您看到了一系列的应用，包括处理客户评论、构建一个应用程序来回答文档问题，甚至使用LLM来决定何时调用外部工具，如Web搜索来回答复杂问题。
In this short course, you saw a range of applications, including processing customer reviews and
如果一两周前，有人问你建立所有这些应用需要多少工作量，我想很多人会觉得，哇，这听起来像是几周，甚至更长时间的工作。
building an application to answer questions over documents, and even using an llm to decide
但是您在这个短课程中看到了，只需要相当数量的代码行，您就可以使用Langtrain相当高效地构建所有这些应用。
when to make a call to an external tool like web search to answer complex questions.
希望您能够借鉴这些想法，也许您可以使用Jupyter笔记本中看到的一些代码片段在自己的应用程序中使用它们。
If a week or two ago, someone had asked you how much work would it be to build all of
而这些想法只是一个开始。
these applications, I think a lot of people thought, boy, this sounds like weeks, maybe
您可以使用语言模型进行许多其他应用。
even longer of work.
这些模型非常强大，因为它们适用于如此广泛的任务，无论是关于CSV的问题，查询SQL数据库，还是与API交互。
But you saw in this short course how with just a pretty reasonable number of lines of
有许多不同的使用链和提示组合以及输出解析器和更多链来在Langtrain中完成所有这些事情的示例。
code, you can use Langtrain to build all of these applications pretty efficiently.
而这大部分归功于Langtrain社区。
As I hope you take these ideas, maybe you can take some code snippets that you saw in
因此，我还要非常感谢社区中的每个人的贡献，无论是改进文档，使其更容易入门，还是新类型的链，开启了一个全新的可能性世界。
the Jupyter notebooks and use them in your own applications.
因此，如果您还没有这样做，请去您的笔记本电脑、台式机上运行pip install Langtrain。
And these ideas are really just the start.
然后使用它来构建一些惊人的应用程序。
There's a lot of other applications that you can use language models for.